cellhut.com 2014-02-13

# CellHut.com's Privacy Policy: How CellHut.com handles your information.

Thank you for shopping with CellHUT.com . We have done our best to ensure the security and privacy of your transactions with us. Rest assured that your credit card information and other personal data will be treated with the highest standards of safety, security, and confidentiality. 

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you-businesses, consumers and the general public-in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us, and to help you make informed decisions when using our web site and all of our related services therein. 

Contact Information To request a correction or deletion of your private information, or if you have any questions and general comments about this privacy policy, please contact us: [info@cellhut.com](mailto:info@cellhut.com)

Mailing address:   
269 Walnut Road  
Glen Cove, NY 11542   
Phone: 516-945-3636   
Fax: 1-212-675-8017  What Information Do We Collect?

When visiting the our web site, you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you voluntarily choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis, and Web site use information gathered on a collective basis as you and others browse our Web site. 

Personal Information You Choose to Provide

Registration Information You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you register to be a user of our services, register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts. 

How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Generally, we use personal information for purposes of managing and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. 

Choice/Opt-out

We allow you the choice to opt-out of having your information used for purposes not directly related to our site, when we ask for the information.

Until you explicitly opt-in for the first time we consider you in the opt-out category. We always notify our customers when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

If you do not wish to receive any promotional or marketing e-mails and/or surface mail marketing letters, you may opt-out of receiving those communications by sending an e-mail with the subject line "Unsubscribe" to  info@cellhut.com. 

What Are Cookies?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?

As you visit our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other customers. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. 

Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

We also use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing credit card payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities. 

How Do We Protect Your Information?

Secure Information Transmissions Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP. 

How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by contact us, see the above contact information. 

What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

Your Consent

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. At any time you may request to view any and all changes and updates, via surface mail. 

Notification of Changes

The Privacy Policy is subject to periodic review and change. In order to view the current Privacy Policy, simply check this section of the website. If we materially change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so users are aware of what information we collect, how it is used, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. In some cases where we post a notice, we may also email user who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

We've made every effort to make our system a secure one. In order to provide our customers with the most secure and private online shopping environment available, CellHUT.com uses state-of-the-art technology to protect credit card numbers and other confidential information you provide when placing an order. Any information that you send to us while at our secure site is "encrypted" before it is transmitted over the web.

 **CellHUT.com** does not sell, rent, or trade customer information, or any other information, which may identify you, to any outside party under any circumstances. Your information is only used to ensure secure ordering and to provide a more personalized shopping experience.

 **CellHUT.com** does not reveal customer information except to complete transactions with our third party banking institution. The banking institution we do banking with is under strict responsibility to keep your information private and protected. 

**CellHUT.com** is committed to providing all customers with a world-class shopping experience. In order to measure how well we are doing and to better serve you with our product offerings, from time-to-time we may contact you via email and solicit your participation in research.

 **CellHUT.com** may also occasionally notify you via email with recommendations or special offers of new products, prices, or any other promotions. You may request to remove yourself from future efforts of this kind at any time.
